Aaron Ziegelman Foundation collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Manuscripts
  - Finding Aid (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Subseries 9: Artifact Documentation
      - A39.1-A39.20. Zim (2 of 3), 17 leaves (Box-folder 40/639)
        14 artifacts
      - A39.2-A39.4, A39.21-A29.30. Zim (3 of 3), 2 leaves, (8 photographs) (Box-folder 40/640)
      - A40.1 - A40.4. Gutman, 1 leaf, (7 photographs) (Box-folder 40/641)
      - A41.1, A41-TBO. Hetman, 31 leaves, (4 photographs) (Box-folder 40/642)
        School records
      - A42.1 – A42.17. Getman, 33 leaves, (14 photographs) (Box-folder 40/643)
      - A 43.1 – A43.4. Prager, 4 photographs (Box-folder 41/644)
      - A44-TBO. Wolyn, 11 photographs (Box-folder 41/645)
      - Missing A45? (Box-folder 41/646)
      - Missing A46? (Box-folder 41/647)
      - A47-TBO. Levensohn (Box-folder 41/648)
      - Missing A48? (Box-folder 41/649)
      - Missing A49? (Box-folder 41/650)
      - Missing A50? (Box-folder 41/651)
      - A51. National Archives (Box-folder 41/652)
      - A52.1. Satyuk, 4 photographs (Box-folder 41/653)
      - A53.1. Halpern, 2 photographs (Box-folder 41/654)
      - A54.1. Woyzuck, 4 leaves, 13 photographs (Box-folder 41/655)
      - A55. Gringurten, 4 leaves (Box-folder 41/656)
        Deed of Gift; Photocopy of a book?
      - A56-TBO. Sherman, 10 leaves (Box-folder 41/657)
      - A57-TBO Jewish Historical Institute, 12 leaves (Box-folder 41/658)
      - A58. Friedman (Box-folder 41/659)
        See oversize box: 2/27
      - A59. Lipszyc (Box-folder 41/660)
        Photocopy of French police record leaving Luboml
      - A60-TBO. Blumen, 4 leaves (Box-folder 41/661)
      - A61-TBO. Volyn Region, 73 leaves (Box-folder 41/662)
      - A62. Moscow Archives, 140 leaves (Box-folder 41/663)
        Photocopies of articles from Russian newspapers
      - A63-TBO. Vitalievich, 3 leaves (Box-folder 41/664)
        Certificate
      - Missing A64 (Box-folder 41/665)
      - A65.1. Maygelikh (Box-folder 41/666)
      - A66.1. Schechter, 2 leaves, (4 photographs) (Box-folder 41/667)
      - Missing A67 (Box-folder 41/668)
      - A68. Newberger (Box-folder 41/669)
        See oversize box: 2/26
      - A69.1 – A69.4. Naygelich (Box-folder 41/670)
        5 artifacts
      - R1.1-R1.8. Dzei, 67 leaves, (16 photographs) (Box-folder 41/671)
        Maps
      - R2.1. Ostapyuk, 3 leaves (Box-folder 41/672)
      - R3. Luboml Museum, 18 leaves (Box-folder 41/673)
        Call to Vote
      - R7. Hoover Institute, 12 leaves, (13 black and white prints, 13 negatives) (Box-folder 41/674)
      - Various Artifact Donations, 11 leaves, (21 prints) (Box-folder 41/675)
      - Edited Drafts of the Letters of the Eiger and Ziegelman Families, 144 leaves (Box-folder 42/676)
        The manuscript materials are in English and unidentified language.
      - Edited Drafts of the Letters of the Eiger and Ziegelman Families, 207 leaves (Box-folder 42/677)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Russian and unidentified language.
      - Letters of the Eiger and Ziegelman Families, 1922-1941 - Bound Copy 1, 126 leaves (Box-folder 42/678)
      - Letters of the Eiger and Ziegelman Families, 1922-1941 - Bound Copy 2, 127 leaves (Box-folder 42/679)
      - Getman, Abraham - Original Letters and Translations, 134 leaves (Box-folder 42/680)
        The materials are in English, Yiddish, Russian, Polish and Hebrew.
      - "Eiger Letters, Bound Translation" (Box-folder 43/681)
      - Eiger Letters from bag labeled “safe” (Box-folder 43/682)
    - Contact Sheets
      - Ziegelman, Aaron, Duplicate prints (Box-folder 43/2251)
      - Wasserman, Fred Duplicate prints, PH1943-2068 (Box-folder 43/2252)
      - Wasserman, Fred Duplicate prints (Box-folder 43/2253)
    - Subjects Files
      - Subject Lists, 14 leaves (Box-folder 44/683)
      - Our Shtetl – Economic Life, 22 leaves (Box-folder 44/684)
        14 photocopied prints and 7 photocopied leaves from Hebrew to Yizkor book
      - Our Shtetl – Early Days, 22 leaves (Box-folder 44/685)
        PH0546, PH0069, PH08, PH0910, PH0466, PH0166, PH0567, PH0912, PH0567, PH0128, 3 photocopied pages from Hebrew to Yizkor book, and PH0248.
      - I. Our Shtetl – Views from Town-Marketplace, 100 leaves (Box-folder 44/686)
        82 photocopies of prints, 1 photocopied page from Hebrew to Yizkor book and 2 maps
      - I. Our Shtetl – Mixed Subjects, 105 leaves (Box-folder 44/687)
        17 photocopies of prints, 2 photocopied leaves from the Hebrew to Yizkor book including other documentation
      - I. Our Shtetl – Serving the Community, 30 leaves (Box-folder 44/688)
        15 photocopies of prints, 1 photocopied page from Hebrew to Yizkor book and other documentation
      - II. Family and Religious Life, 37 leaves (Box-folder 44/689)
        32 leaves of images and 1 photocopied page from Hebrew to Yizkor book
      - II. Family and Religious Life – Mixed Subjects, 81 leaves (Box-folder 44/690)
        35 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation
      - II. Family and Religious Life – Making a Home, 19 leaves (Box-folder 44/691)
        18 photocopies of prints
      - II. Family and Religious Life – Sabbath and Holidays, 15 leaves (Box-folder 44/692)
        8 photocopies of prints and 6 photocopied leaves from Hebrew to Yizkor book.
      - III. Youth – Mixed Subjects, 53 leaves (Box-folder 44/693)
        45 photocopies of prints and 2 photocopied leaves from Hebrew to Yizkor book and other visual documentation.
      - III. Youth – Recreation, 19 leaves (Box-folder 44/694)
        12 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation.
      - III. Youth – Zionism, 60 leaves (Box-folder 44/695)
        48 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation.
      - III. Youth – Education, 32 leaves (Box-folder 44/696)
        23 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation and 8 photocopied leaves from Hebrew to Yizkor book.
      - III. Youth – Culture, 19 leaves (Box-folder 44/697)
        12 photocopies of prints, 1 photocopied page from Hebrew to Yizbor other visual documentation.
      - IV. Leaving Luboml Emigration and Aliyah, 60 leaves (Box-folder 44/698)
        43 photocopies of prints, 3 photocopied leaves from Hebrew to Yizkor book and other visual documentation.
      - IV. Leaving Luboml – The Ties That Bind, 7 leaves (Box-folder 44/699)
        6 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation.
      - IV. Leaving Luboml, 46 leaves (Box-folder 44/700)
        8 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation.
      - V. War, Destruction, and Survival, 13 leaves (Box-folder 44/701)
        3 photocopies of prints, 3 photocopied leaves from Hebrew to Yizbor book and other visual documentation
      - V. War, Destruction, and Survival, 23 leaves (Box-folder 44/702)
        2 photocopies of prints, 4 photocopied leaves from Hebrew to Yizbor book and other visual documentation
      - VI. “The Return to Life” – Memorials, 5 leaves (Box-folder 44/703)
        3 photocopies of prints, 1 photocopied page from Hebrew to Yizbor book and other visual documentation
      - VI. “The Return to Life” – Survivors Return, 4 leaves (Box-folder 44/704)
        4 photocopies of prints
      - VI. “The Return to Life” – New Lives, 34 leaves (Box-folder 45/705)
        29 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation
      - VI. “The Return to Life” – DP Camps, 20 leaves (Box-folder 45/706)
        12 photocopies of prints, 1 photocopied page from Hebrew to Yizbor book and other visual documentation
      - VI. New Lives, 37 leaves (Box-folder 45/707)
        26 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation
      - Soldiers, 14 leaves (Box-folder 45/708)
        14 photocopies of prints
      - Jewish Sites/Traces in Luboml, 9 leaves (Box-folder 45/709)
        7 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation
      - Recent Return Visits, 2 leaves (Box-folder 45/710)
        1 photocopy of print and caption
      - Non Jewish Life, 11 leaves (Box-folder 45/711)
        11 photocopies of prints
      - Family Portraits, 134 leaves (Box-folder 45/712)
        132 photocopies of prints and other visual documentation
    - Photocopies
      - PH0001– P1.9, Guz, 23 leaves (Box-folder 46/713)
      - PH0009– PH0015, Shalev, 15 leaves (Box-folder 46/714)
      - PH0016– PH0020, Elfand, 11 leaves (Box-folder 46/715)
      - PH0021– PH0027, Elfand, 15 leaves (Box-folder 46/716)
      - PH0028– PH0048, Zeigelbaum, 48 leaves (Box-folder 46/717)
      - PH0049– PH0061, Roz, 30 leaves (Box-folder 46/718)
      - PH0062– PH0074, Blau (Weiner), 35 leaves (Box-folder 46/719)
      - PH0075– PH0096, Kandelshtein, 54 leaves (Box-folder 46/720)
      - PH0097– PH0108, Shinal, 28 leaves (Box-folder 46/721)
      - PH0109– PH0128, Erlich, 45 leaves (Box-folder 46/722)
      - PH0129– PH0139, Giladi, 25 leaves (Box-folder 46/723)
      - PH0140 – PH0143, Melamed, 9 leaves (Box-folder 46/724)
      - PH0144– PH0149, Jucht, 18 leaves (Box-folder 46/725)
      - PH0150– 14.17, Bokser, 42 leaves (Box-folder 46/726)
      - PH0166– PH0167, Seidel, 9 leaves (Box-folder 46/727)
      - PH0168 – PH0169, Langer, 8 leaves (Box-folder 46/728)
      - PH0170– PH0194, Wolyn, 86 leaves (Box-folder 46/729)
      - PH0195– PH0245, Karpus, 129 leaves (Box-folder 46/730)
      - PH0246– PH0248, Hatefutsoth, 10 leaves (Box-folder 46/731)
      - PH0249– PH0254, Yad Vashem, 16 leaves (Box-folder 46/732)
      - PH0255– PH0256, Jabutinsky Institute, 4 leaves (Box-folder 46/733)
      - PH0257– PH0259, Sylvia, 10 leaves (Box-folder 46/734)
      - PH0260– PH0263, Haghetaot, 8 leaves (Box-folder 46/735)
      - PH0264– PH0284, Friedman, 42 leaves (Box-folder 47/736)
      - PH0285– PH0294, Kandelshain, 27 leaves (Box-folder 47/737)
      - PH0295– PH0303, Rosenblott, 22 leaves (Box-folder 47/738)
      - PH0304, Zimmerberg, 3 leaves (Box-folder 47/739)
      - PH0305– PH0312, Eiger, 25 leaves (Box-folder 47/740)
      - PH0313– P29.9, Trent, 24 leaves (Box-folder 47/741)
      - PH0320– PH0328, Swerdloff, 19 leaves (Box-folder 47/742)
      - PH0329 – PH0336, Zucker, 17 leaves (Box-folder 47/743)
      - PH0337– PH0343, Blumen, 18 leaves (Box-folder 47/744)
      - PH0344– PH0358, Nussenblatt, 40 leaves (Box-folder 47/745)
      - PH0359– PH0377, Kostin, 44 leaves (Box-folder 47/746)
      - PH0378– PH0380, Bracha, 8 leaves (Box-folder 47/747)
      - PH0381– PH0396, Julius, 33 leaves (Box-folder 47/748)
      - PH0397– PH0401, Krien, 13 leaves (Box-folder 47/749)
      - P38.1 – P38.2, Teitlebaum, 2 leaves (Box-folder 47/750)
      - PH0402– PH0456, Uberman, 149 leaves (Box-folder 47/751)
      - PH0457– PH0463, Montevideo, 16 leaves (Box-folder 47/752)
      - PH0464– PH0467, Zimberberg, 12 leaves (Box-folder 47/753)
      - PH0468– PH0543, Golod, 180 leaves (Box-folder 47/754)
      - PH0544– PH0545, Central Archives, 5 leaves (Box-folder 47/755)
      - PH0546– PH0593, Sobel, 112 leaves (Box-folder 48/756)
      - PH0594– PH0608, Ziegelman, 59 leaves (Box-folder 48/757)
        Contains photocopies of photographs that were not copied for the exhibition
      - PH0609– PH0654, Chanales, 110 leaves (Box-folder 48/758)
      - PH0655– PH0695, Kessler, 89 leaves (Box-folder 48/759)
      - PH0696– PH0716, Eiger, 44 leaves (Box-folder 48/760)
      - PH0717– PH0768, Gershengorn, 127 leaves (Box-folder 48/761)
      - PH0769– PH0774, Wolkun, 15 leaves (Box-folder 48/762)
      - PH0775– PH0783, Zimmerberg, 29 leaves (Box-folder 48/763)
      - PH0784– PH0790, Tessler, 15 leaves (Box-folder 48/764)
      - PH0791– PH0793, YIVO Institute for Jewish Research, 6 leaves (Box-folder 48/765)
      - PH0794 – PH0833, Getman, 107 leaves (Box-folder 48/766)
      - PH0834– PH0854, Polska Akademia Nauk, Instytut Sztuki, 65 leaves (Box-folder 49/767)
      - PH0855– PH0862, Glickman, 29 leaves (Box-folder 49/768)
      - PH0863 – PH0909, Brawet, 102 leaves (Box-folder 49/769)
      - PH0910– PH0921, Bokser, 31 leaves (Box-folder 49/770)
      - PH0922– PH0939, Cinder, 52 leaves (Box-folder 49/771)
      - PH0941– PH0950, Orbuch, 32 leaves (Box-folder 49/772)
      - PH0951– PH0963, Kraut, 39 leaves (Box-folder 49/773)
      - PH0964– PH0967, Lipszyc, 9 leaves (Box-folder 49/774)
      - PH0968– PH0976, Perelman, 18 leaves (Box-folder 49/775)
      - PH0977, Huz, 2 leaves (Box-folder 49/776)
      - PH0978– PH0984, Ingber, 23 leaves (Box-folder 49/777)
      - PH0985– PH1000, Gutman, 38 leaves (Box-folder 49/778)
      - PH1001– PH1013, Buchstein, 29 leaves (Box-folder 49/779)
      - PH1014– PH1021, Lindenboym, 18 leaves (Box-folder 49/780)
      - PH1022, Lichtmacher, 2 leaves (Box-folder 49/781)
      - PH1023, Siegelman, 3 leaves (Box-folder 49/782)
      - PH1024– PH1027, Rosenbluth, 17 leaves (Box-folder 49/783)
      - PH1028 – PH1030, Gitalis, 11 leaves (Box-folder 49/784)
      - PH1031– PH1051, Rosenzweig, 58 leaves (Box-folder 49/785)
      - PH1053– PH1054, Halpern, 3 leaves (Box-folder 49/786)
      - PH1055– PH1065, Axelrod, 22 leaves (Box-folder 50/787)
      - PH1066– PH1076, Ginsburg, 19 leaves (Box-folder 50/788)
      - PH1077– PH1078, Levine, 4 leaves (Box-folder 50/789)
      - PH1079– PH1087, Meller, 29 leaves (Box-folder 50/790)
      - PH1088– PH1097, Schimmel, 30 leaves (Box-folder 50/791)
      - PH1098– PH1115, Hetman, 53 leaves (Box-folder 50/792)
      - PH1116– PH1128, Schuster Goodman, 44 leaves (Box-folder 50/793)
      - PH1129– PH1154, Dzei (1 of 2), 82 leaves (Box-folder 50/794)
      - PH1155– PH1199, Dzei (2 of 2), 142 leaves (Box-folder 50/795)
      - PH1202– PH1240, Ostapyuk, 144 leaves (Box-folder 50/796)
      - PH1241– PH1258, Luboml Museum, 41 leaves (Box-folder 51/797)
      - PH1259– PH1263, Kaminska, 11 leaves (Box-folder 51/798)
      - PH1264– PH1266, Kotler, 7 leaves (Box-folder 51/799)
      - PH1267, Satsvk, 2 leaves (Box-folder 51/800)
      - PH1268– PH1282, Borman, 32 leaves (Box-folder 51/801)
      - PH1283– PH1303, Luck Archives, 43 leaves (Box-folder 51/802)
      - PH1304– PH1308, Jewish Historical Institute, 12 leaves (Box-folder 51/803)
      - PH1309– PH1310, Becker, 5 leaves (Box-folder 51/804)
      - PH1311– PH1320, Prager, 35 leaves (Box-folder 51/805)
      - PH1321– PH1330, Samberg, 38 leaves (Box-folder 51/806)
      - PH1332– PH1334, Rodman, 10 leaves (Box-folder 51/807)
      - PH1335– PH1342, Friedman, 22 leaves (Box-folder 51/808)
      - PH1343– PH1347, Glass, 13 leaves (Box-folder 51/809)
      - PH1348, Popek, 3 leaves (Box-folder 51/810)
      - PH1350, Archiwum Documentary Mechanicznej, 3 leaves (Box-folder 51/811)
      - PH1351– PH1359, Plotnik, 22 leaves (Box-folder 51/812)
      - PH1360– PH1364, Schechter, 11 leaves (Box-folder 51/813)
      - PH1365, Roiter, 2 leaves (Box-folder 51/814)
      - PH1366– PH1373, Reimer, 22 leaves. (Box-folder 51/815)
      - PH1374– PH1375, Newberger, 7 leaves (Box-folder 51/816)
      - PH1376– PH1383, MJH/Posner, 25 leaves (Box-folder 51/817)
- Oversized manuscript materials
  - Forward, December 15, 1995 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Polish newspaper (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Jewish Journal 10, No. 36 (November 3-9, 1995). (Box-folder 1/3)
  - The Jewish Week, October 13, 1995 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Jewish Exponent 199, No. 15 (April 11, 1996). (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Map of Luboml (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Yizkor Book pub, (7/7) (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Poster for Book: The Memorial Box of a Vanished Shtetl (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Children of the Holocust (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Luboml martyrs (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Luboml/An-sky (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Cardoza: Ruth Messinger proclamation (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Posters: Luboml: A Small Jewish World (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Remembering Libivne (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Remembering Libivne (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Newspaper articles: Trip to Luboml (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Remembering Luboml (Box-folder 1/17)
  - A12 and A26 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Luboml exhibit case furniture and mount specifications (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Cardozo Texts (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Cardozo alternate quote panels (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Cardozo final texts (Box-folder 2/22)
  - Luboml directory (Box-folder 2/23)
  - A51, National Archives (Box-folder 2/24)
  - A20, Tessler (Box-folder 2/25)
  - A68, Newberger (Box-folder 2/26)
  - A58, Friedman (Box-folder 2/27)
  - Cardozo exhibition maps (Box-folder 2/28)
  - Gershman Y- Ragone, Keith (3/3), Exhibitions (Box-folder 2/29)
  - A17 and A66 (Box-folder 2/30)
  - Maps (Box 3)
    14 oversize folders of various sizes containing maps of Poland.
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Chanales, Lillian, AFC 2003/002: SR001; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Chanales, Lillian, AFC 2003/002: SR002; Tape 3, audio cassette
  - Eiger, Nathan, AFC 2003/002: SR003; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Eiger, Nathan, AFC 2003/002: SR004; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Eiger, Nathan, AFC 2003/002: SR005; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Gershengorn, Ann, AFC 2003/002: SR006; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Gershengorn, Ann, AFC 2003/002: SR007; Tape 3, audio cassette
  - Gershengorn, Victor, AFC 2003/002: SR008; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Gershengorn, Victor, AFC 2003/002: SR009; Tape 3, audio cassette
  - Gershengorn, Victor, AFC 2003/002: SR010; Tape 4-5, audio cassette
  - Getman, Abe, AFC 2003/002: SR011; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Getman, Abe, AFC 2003/002: SR012; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Getman, Abe, AFC 2003/002: SR013; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Getman, Abe, AFC 2003/002: SR014; Tape 7-8, audio cassette
  - Goodman, May Shuster, AFC 2003/002: SR015; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Goodman, May Shuster 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: SR016; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Goodman, May Shuster 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: SR017; Tape 5, audio cassette
  - Karpus 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: SR018; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Karpus, AFC 2003/002: SR019; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Karpus, AFC 2003/002: SR020; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Karpus, AFC 2003/002: SR021; Tape 7-8, audio cassette
  - Kessler, Esther, AFC 2003/002: SR022; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Kessler, Esther, AFC 2003/002: SR023; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Kessler, Esther, AFC 2003/002: SR024; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Lichtmacher, Victor, AFC 2003/002: SR025; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Lichtmacher, Victor, AFC 2003/002: SR026; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Lichtmacher, Victor, AFC 2003/002: SR027; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Lichtmacher, Victor, AFC 2003/002: SR028; Tape 7, audio cassette
  - Meller, Bernard, AFC 2003/002: SR029; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Meller, Bernard, AFC 2003/002: SR030; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Meller, Bernard 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: SR031; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Meller, Bernard 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: SR032; Tape 7-8, audio cassette
  - Pachter, Esther 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: SR033; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Pachter, Esther 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: SR034; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Pachter, Esther 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: SR035; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Posner, Clara 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: SR036; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Posner, Clara, AFC 2003/002: SR037; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Posner, Clara, AFC 2003/002: SR038; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Rosenzweig, Benjamin, AFC 2003/002: SR039; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Rosenzweig, Benjamin, AFC 2003/002: SR040; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Rosenzweig, Benjamin, AFC 2003/002: SR041; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Rosenzweig, Benjamin, AFC 2003/002: SR042; Tape 7, audio cassette
  - Shalev, Moshe, AFC 2003/002: SR043; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Shalev, Moshe, AFC 2003/002: SR044; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Shalev, Moshe, AFC 2003/002: SR045; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Sobel, Nathan, AFC 2003/002: SR046; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Sobel, Nathan, AFC 2003/002: SR047; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Sobel, Nathan, AFC 2003/002: SR048; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Nathan Sobel, AFC 2003/002: SR049; Tape 7-8, audio cassette
  - Sobel, Nathan, AFC 2003/002: SR050; Tape 9, audio cassette
  - Ziegelman, Aaron, AFC 2003/002: SR051; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Ziegelman, Aaron, AFC 2003/002: SR052; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Ziegelman, Aaron, AFC 2003/002: SR053; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - “Luboml,”, AFC 2003/002: SR054; Tape 1, audio cassette
    Aaron Ziegelman and Fred Wasserman on “Radio Times”, WHYY in Philadelphia
  - Shildergemeyn, Boreth 1997-03-07, AFC 2003/002: SR055; Tape 1, audio cassette
    Boreth Shildergemyn interviewed at home in Queens by Michael Alpert
  - Shildergemeyn, Boreth 1982-05-06, AFC 2003/002: SR056; Tape 2, audio cassette
    Boreth Shildergemyn interviewed at home in Queens
  - Ebers, Pesya 1982-08-02, AFC 2003/002: SR057; Tape 1, audio cassette
  - Karpus, Joseph and Rifka with Moshe Shaler, 1994-10-17, AFC 2003/002: SR058; audio cassette
    Interview with Joseph and Rifka Karpus, Moshe Shaler
  - Zim, Ethel 1994-10-16, AFC 2003/002: SR059; audio cassette
  - Patiyevick, Vladimir 1995-09-12, AFC 2003/002: SR060; audio cassette
    on the same tape as Maria From Greengurten
  - Ingber, Leah and Jerry 1995-09-13, AFC 2003/002: SR061; audio cassette
    Leah Kejilis Ingber interviewed by Jerry Ingber (son) and Meisals, Yaacor (Leah’s brother-in-law) Leah Kejilis Ingber interviewed by Jerry Ingber (son) and Meisals, Yaacor (Leah’s brother-in-law)
  - Ziegelman, Aaron 1973-01/02, AFC 2003/002: SR062; Tape 1, audio microcassette
    Interview with Ziegelman about his visit to Luboml
  - Ziegelman, Aaron 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: SR063; Tape 2, audio microcassette
    Interview about his visit to Luboml
  - Ziegelman, Aaron 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: SR064; Tape 3, audio microcassette
  - Ziegelman, Aaron 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: SR065; Tape 4, audio microcassette
  - Ziegelman, Aaron 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: SR066; Tape 1, audio cassette
    Interview about Luboml on Yiddish radio,
  - Plotnik, Riwa 1997-06-29, AFC 2003/002: SR067; Tape 1-2, audio cassette
  - Plotnik, Riwa 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: SR068; Tape 3-4, audio cassette
  - Plotnik, Riwa 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: SR069; Tape 5-6, audio cassette
  - Plotnik, Riwa 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: SR070; Tape 7, audio cassette
- Series 3: Graphic materials
  See PDF for a complete listing of photo descriptions.
  - Guz, 8 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0001–PH0008 (Box-folder 52/818)
    Materials donated by Pinkhas Guz
  - Shalev, 7 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0009-PH0015 (Box-folder 52/819)
    Materials donated by Moshe Shalev
  - Elfand, 5 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0016-PH0020 (Box-folder 52/820)
    Materials donated by Frieda Elfand
  - Efrat, 1 contact print and 7 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0021–PH0027 (Box-folder 52/821)
    Materials donated by Moshe Efrat
  - Zeigelbaum Ingber, 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0028-PH0037, PH0039 – PH0040, PH0042 – PH0048 (Box-folder 52/822)
    Materials donated by Miriam Zeigelbaum Ingber
  - Roz, 13 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0049-PH0061 (Box-folder 52/823)
    Materials donated by Bella Roz
  - Blau-Weiner, 13 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0062-PH0074 (Box-folder 52/824)
    Materials donated by Nechama Blau-Weiner
  - Kandelshtein (1 of 2), 21 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0075-PH0096 (Box-folder 52/825)
    Materials donated by Eliahu Kandelshain
  - Kandelshtein (2 of 2), 12 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0097-PH0108 (Box-folder 52/826)
    Materials donated by Batsheva (Bat-Sheva?) Shinal
  - Erlich, 20 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0109-PH0128 (Box-folder 52/827)
    Materials donated by Menachem (Menacham?) Erlich
  - Giladi, 11 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0129-PH0139 (Box-folder 52/828)
    Materials donated by Prina Giladi (Royter
  - Melamed, 3 prints from negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH0140-PH0143 (Box-folder 52/829)
    Materials donated by Klara Melamed